Guide to the News Service Biographical Files, circa 1930s - 2004 UA.27.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Fellows, Robert E., Jr. (Box 18)
- Felsman, Kirk (Box 73)
- Felton, Gayle Carlton (Box 73)
- Fendt, Paul F. (Box 18)
- Fendt, Paul F. (Box 73)
- Fendt, Paul F. (Box 128)
- Fenton, Charles A. (Box 18)
- Fenton, Charles A. (Box 128)
- Ferejohn, Michael T. (Box 73)
- Ferguson, Arthur B. (Box 73)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: History, Effective 9/31/1983
- Ferguson, Arthur Bowles (Box 18)
- Ferguson, Arthur Bowles (Box 128)
- Ferguson, Charles E. (Box 18)
- Ferguson, Charles E. (Box 73)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Mathematical Economics
- Ferguson, Charles E. (Box 128)
- Ferguson, George B. (Box 18)
- Ferguson, George B. (Box 128)
- Ferguson, George B. (Box 149)
- Ferguson, John F. (Box 73)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pratt, 2002
- Ferguson, Oliver (Box 149)
- Ferguson, Oliver Watkins (Box 128)
- Ferguson, Oliver Watkins (Box 73)
- Ferrari, Heriberto Alfredo (Box 18)
- Ferraro, Thomas Joseph (Box 128)
- Ferraro, Thomas Joseph (Box 73)
- Ferree-Clark, Nancy (Box 128)
- Ferree-Clark, Nancy (Box 73)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Duke Chapel
- Ferrell, Jesse W. (Box 18)
- Ferrell, Ron P. (Box 73)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: University Photographer
- Ferriero, David (Box 73)
- Fetter, Bernard F. (Box 149)
- Fetter, Bernard Frank (Box 128)
- Fetter, Bernard Frank (Box 73)
- Fetters, (Captain) James C. (Box 128)
- Fetters, James C. (Box 18)
- Fetters, James C. (Box 149)
- Feussner, John R. (Box 73)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: DUMC and VA Medied Ctr.
- Few, Ben F. (Box 128)
- Few, Ben F., Trustee (Box 116)
- Few, Eugene C. (Box 18)
- Few, William Preston, 4 folders (Box 18)
- Fielding, Sara (Box 128)
- Fielding, Sara (Box 73)
- Fierke, Carol (Box 73)
- Fike, Edward L. (Box 18)
- Fike, Edward L. (Box 149)
- Fike, Edward L. (Box 128)
- Fillmore, Paul G. (Box 18)
- Fillmore, Paul G. (Box 128)
- Fillmore, Paul G. (Box 149)
- Fillmore, Richard (Box 18)
- Fillmore, Richard (Box 128)
- Fillmore, Richard (Box 149)
- Filston, Howard C. (Box 73)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Thoracic and Pediatric Surgery
- Finch, Thomas A. (Box 128)
- Finch, Thomas A., Trustee (Box 116)
- Fine, Robert Lance (Box 73)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medicine and Pharmacology
- Finger, Joseph Michael (Box 73)
- Finnell, Dallas G. (Box 18)
- Finnell, Dallas G. (Box 128)
- Finucci, Valeria (Box 73)
- First, Joan (Box 18)
- Fischer, Karla (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Law and Psychology
- Fish, Peter G. (Box 73)
- Fish, Peter G. (Box 128)
- Fish, Stanley Eugene (Box 128)
- Fish, Stanley Eugene (Box 73)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: English, 1985-2000
- Fishbaugh, Ronald L. (Box 18)
- Fishbaugh, Ronald L. (Box 128)
- Fishbaugh, Ronald L. (Box 149)
- Fisher, Albert (Box 74)
- Fisher, Albert F. (Box 128)
- Fisher, Edgar Jacob (Box 18)
- Fisher, Edgar Jacob (Box 128)
- Fisher, Edgar Jacob (Box 149)
- Fisher, John H. (Box 18)
- Fisher, John H. (Box 128)
- Fisher, John H. (Box 74)
- Fishman, Sue Horan (Box 128)
- Fishman, Sue Horan (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Student Activities
- Fitch, Robert D. (Box 74)
- Fitz, John G. (Box 74)
- Fitzgerald, Michael (Box 74)
- Fitzgerald, William Stone (Box 18)
- Fitzpatrick, David (Box 74)
- Fjeld, Jon (Box 18)
- Flanagan, Eleanor (Box 18)
- Flanagan, Eleanor (Box 128)
- Flanagan, Owen (Box 74)
- Flath, Daniel Evans (Box 74)
- Flatter, Pat (Box 149)
- Fleishman, Joel Lawrence, 1971-2001 (Box 74)
- Fleishman, Joel Lawrence (Box 128)
- Flint, Weston (Box 18)
- Flint, Weston (Box 128)
- Flowers, Anne (Box 18)
- Flowers, Anne (Box 128)
- Flowers, Maxine Rogers (Box 128)
- Flowers, Maxine Rogers (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychiatric Social Work
- Flowers, Robert Lee, 3 folders (Box 18)
- Flowers, Robert Lee (Box 128)
- Flowers, Robert Lee (Box 149)
- Flowers, W. W., Trustee (Box 116)
- Floyd, W. Harvey (Box 19)
- Floyd, Walter Lawrence (Box 128)
- Floyd, Walter Lawrence (Box 74)
- Fluke, Donald J. (Box 128)
- Fluke, Donald J. (Box 74)
- Foeckler, Merle M. (Box 19)
- Foerster, Norman (Box 19)
- Fogleman, Paul (Box 74)
- Folger, Fred (Box 74)
- Folger, Fred (Box 129)
- Follis, Richard (Box 19)
- Folsom, James M. (Box 129)
- Folsom, James W. (Box 19)
- Folsom, Reid (Box 19)
- Folsom, Reid (Box 129)
- Folz, Rodney J. (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pulmonary Medicine
- Forbus, Wiley D. (Box 19)
- Forbus, Wiley D. (Box 129)
- Forbus, Wiley D. (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pathology, Retired 9/1/1964; died 3/3/1976
- Ford, Joel C. (Box 19)
- Ford, Joel C., Jr. (Box 149)
- Ford, Joel C., Jr. (Box 129)
- Forlines, John Arthur (Box 74)
- Forsyth, John D. (Box 129)
- Forsyth, John D. (Box 74)
- Fortier, Kenneth J. (Box 74)
- Fortier, Kenneth J. (Box 129)
- Fortin, Donald (Box 74)
- Fortney, Lloyd (Box 19)
- Fortney, Lloyd Ray (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Physics, died3/7/1999
- Forton, Gerald T. (Box 129)
- Forton, Gerald T. (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Dietary Services, DUMC
- Fortune, Ellen G. (Box 74)
- Forward, Richard B., Jr. (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biology/Zoology, Marine Lab., Beaufort
- Foster, Andrew Durwood (Box 19)
- Foster, Andrew Durwood (Box 129)
- Foster, Andrew Durwood (Box 149)
- Foster, Andrew Durwood, Jr. (Box 74)
- Foster, Bill (Box 19)
- Foster, C. Allen (Box 74)
- Foster, Darrell V. (Box 74)
- Foster, F. Douglas (Box 74)
- Foster, Ludmila Alexandrovna (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Slavic Languages
- Foster, William L. (Box 74)
- Foulks, Gary Neal (Box 74)
- Fousek, Marianka K. (Box 74)
- Fouts, Nevin (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Fuqua, 1999
- Fowler, Donald R. (Box 74)
- Fowler, Earl (Box 149)
- Fowler, Earle C. (Box 19)
- Fowler, Earle Cabell (Box 129)
- Fowler, Earle Cabell (Box 74)
- Fowler, Edward Blair (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Center for International Studies
- Fowler, John A. (Box 19)
- Fowler, John A. (Box 149)
- Fowler, John A. (Box 74)
- Fowler, John A. (Box 129)
- Fowler, Marshall (Box 19)
- Fowlie, Wallace (Box 19)
- Fowlie, Wallace (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: French Literature, died 8/16/1998
- Fowlkes, H. Lee (Box 74)
- Fox, Adrienne (Box 19)
- Fox, Elisabeth June (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Clinical Anesthesiology
- Fox, John W. (Box 19)
- Fox, Richard G. (Box 74)
- Fox, Richard G. (Box 129)
- Fox. James Joseph (Box 74)
- Frances, Allen (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychiatry and Behavioral Sciences
- Francis, Garrick Codrington (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Office of Government Relations and Community Affairs
- Francis, Jennifer (Box 74)
- Frank, Gerald D. (Box 74)
- Frank, Michael M. (Box 74)
- Franklin, John Hope (Box 112)
  Biographical information. Professor; Historian; Author; Endowment Trustee, 1980-1999
- Franks, Carl (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Head Football Coach
- Franzoni, Linda (Box 74)
- Frarey, Carlyle (Box 19)
- Frarey, Charles, Jr. (Box 129)
- Fraser-Reid, Bertram Oliver (Box 74)
- Frederick, Donald G. (Box 74)
- Fredrickson, Barbara L. (Box 74)
- Freedman, Jonathan H. (Box 74)
- Freeman, Curtis (Box 74)
- Freeman, Jay N. (Box 74)
- Freeman, Jay N. (Box 129)
- Freeman, John (Box 19)
- Freemark, Michael (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Endocrinology, Pediatrics
- Freetag, William P. (Box 74)
- Freiburghouse, Leonard F. (Box 19)
- French, John (Box 74)
- Frenzel, C. (Box 149)
- Frenzel, Charles H. (Box 74)
- Frenzel, Charles, Jr. (Box 129)
- Frenzel, Charles, Jr. (Box 19)
- Freundlich, Irwin (Box 19)
- Frey, Kip (Box 74)
- Fridovich, Irwin (Box 74)
- Friedberg, Ruth (Box 19)
- Friedberg, Ruth (Box 74)
- Friedberg, Ruth (Box 129)
- Friedberg, Samuel (Box 19)
- Friedl, Ernestine (Box 129)
- Friedl, Ernestine (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: TCAS; Anthropology
- Friedlander, Walter (Box 19)
- Friedlander, Walter (Box 129)
- Friedman, Allan Howard (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Neurosurgery, 2001
- Friedman, Gregg A. (Box 19)
- Friedman, Henry S. (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Hematology, Oncology, Pediatrics; Pathology
- Friedman, Nancy E. (Box 74)
- Friedrich, John A., 2 folders (Box 19)
- Friedrich, John A. (Box 129)
- Friedrich, John A. (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Health, P. E. and Recreation Dept.
- Friedrich, John A. (Box 149)
- Frizzelle, J. P. (Box 129)
- Frizzelle, J. P., Trustee 1937-58 (Box 116)
- Frothingham, Thomas Eliot (Box 74)
- Frye, John (Box 19)
- Frye, John (Box 129)
- Fuchs, Herbert E. (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Neurosurgery; Asst Pediatrics
- Fulkerson, Mary McClintock (Box 129)
- Fulkerson, Mary McClintock (Box 74)
- Fulkerson, William J., Jr. (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: DUMC and Duke PDC
- Fuller, J. Peyton (Box 129)
- Fuller, J. Peyton (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Planning and Analysis and Univ. Treasurer
- Fulton, Charles Darby, Jr. (Box 74)
- Fulton, Charles Darby, Jr. (Box 129)
- Fultz, Saylor J. (Jim) (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Controller of General Accounts
- Funderburk, Laney (Box 19)
- Funderburk, M. Laney (Box 129)
- Funderburk, M. Laney (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Alumni Affairs
- Fuqua, John Brooks (Box 74)
- Fuqua, John Brooks (Box 129)
- Fuqua, John Brooks, Trustee (Box 116)
- Furbish, William James (Box 19)
- Furbish, William James (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff, Retired 3/1/1983
- Furlow, John A. (Box 19)
- Furlow, John A. (Box 129)
- Fuson, Robert L. (Box 19)
- Fuson, Robert L. (Box 129)
- Futhey, Tracy (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Information Technology, 2001
- Futreal, Andrew (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Molecular Geneticist
- Gadde, Kishore (Box 74)
- Gaede, Jane Taylor (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Clinical Pathology
- Gaffron, Mercedes (Box 19)
- Gaines, Jane Marie (Box 74)
- Galifianakis, Nick (Box 112)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; Law; Politician
- Gall, Stanley (Box 19)
- Gallagher, James J. (Box 19)
- Gallagher, John P. (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Computer Education Center, Fuqua
- Gallemore, John (Box 19)
- Gallemore, John (Box 129)
- Gallie, Thomas Muir (Box 129)
- Gallie, Thomas Muir (Box 74)
- Gallis, Harry Anthony (Box 74)
- Gan, Tong Joo (Box 74)
- Gann, Pamela B. (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: and Law
- Gann, Pamela B. (Box 129)
- Gao, Bai (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Sociology, 1998
- Garber, Paul, 2 folders (Box 19)
- Garbutt, John T., Jr. (Box 74)
- Garcia-Blanco, Mariano (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pharm. and Cancer Bio; Microbio.; Res. of Medicine
- Garci-Gomez, Miguel (Box 74)
- Garci-Gomez, Miguel (Box 129)
- Gardiner, Ann Henshaw (Box 19)
- Gardner, Carl L. (Box 74)
- Gardner, Clarence E., Jr. (Box 19)
- Gardner, Clarence E., Jr. (Box 74)
- Gardner, Clarence E., Jr. (Box 129)
- Gardner, Grant W. (Box 74)
- Gardner, William H. (Box 74)
- Gardner, William H. (Box 129)
- Garg, Davendra P. (Box 129)
- Garg, Davendra P. (Box 74)
- Garmezy, Norman (Box 20)
- Garrard, Anne (Box 20)
- Garrard, Anne (Box 129)
- Garrard, Anne (Box 149)
- Garrett, Nathan T., Trustee July 1977 (Box 116)
- Garrett, William E. (Box 74)
- Garrison, Edwin R. (Box 74)
- Garson, Arthur "Tim," Jr. (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pediatric Cardiology; Health Affairs
- Garst, Jennifer (Box 74)
- Gaspar, David Barry (Box 74)
- Gates, Arthur Mathews (Box 20)
- Gates, Henry Louis "Skip," Jr. (Box 74)
- Gates, Melinda French (Box 129)
- Gates, Melinda French, Trustee (Box 116)
- Gatling, Eva Ingersoll (Box 20)
- Gauer, Otto Hans (Box 20)
- Gauthier, Daniel J. (Box 74)
- Gavin, James R. III, Trustee (Box 116)
- Gavins, Raymond (Box 129)
- Gavins, Raymond (Box 74)
- Gay, Francis Norman "Frank" (Box 129)
- Gay, Francis Norman "Frank" (Box 74)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Personnel, DUMC, 1967
- Geer, Bennett E. (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Endowment Trustee, Effective 12/11/1924
- Gehman, Ila (Box 20)
- Gehman, Ila (Box 129)
- Gehman, W. Scott (Box 20)
- Gehman, W. Scott (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychology, Education
- Gehman, W. Scott (Box 129)
- Geist, Robert M., III (Box 20)
- Geist, Robert M., III (Box 75)
- Gelenbe, Erol (Box 75)
- Gelfand, Alan (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Stats and Decision Sciences
- Geller, Henry (Box 75)
- Geller, Matthew M. (Box 75)
- Gellhorn, Ernest A.E. (Box 75)
- Gellhorn, Ernest A.E. (Box 20)
- Gentry, William Doyle (Box 20)
- George, Linda Kay Kaufman (Box 75)
- George, Rhett T., Jr. (Box 75)
- George, Timothy (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Neurosurgery, 1998
- Georgiade, Gregory S. (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Gen. and Thoracic Surgery, and Plastic Surgery
- Georgiade, Nicholas (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Plastic Surgery
- Gerber, Gerald E. (Box 20)
- Gerber, Gerald E. (Box 129)
- Gerber, Linda H. (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Alumni Affairs and Univ. Development
- Gereffi, Gary (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Sociology, 2001
- Gergen, David (Box 75)
- Gergen, John J. (Box 20)
- Gerhard, Hans W. (Box 20)
- Gerhard, Hans W. (Box 129)
- Gerhard, Hans W. (Box 149)
- German, Deborah Campano (Box 20)
- German, Lawrence D. (Box 20)
- Germino, Barbara (Box 20)
- Gerstle, Frank (Box 20)
- Gerstle, Frank (Box 129)
- Gerstle, Frank (Box 149)
- Geweke, John F. (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Economics; Stats and Decision Sciences
- Gewirth, Daniel Tilton (Box 75)
- Gheith, Jehanne (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Slavic Dept.
- Ghiradelli, Robert G. (Box 75)
- Ghodes, Clarence Frank Louis (Box 149)
- Giannini, Richard C. (Box 20)
- Giannini, Richard C. (Box 149)
- Giannitrapani, Duilio (Box 20)
- Giannitrapani, Duilio (Box 129)
- Giannitrapani, Duilio (Box 149)
- Gianturco, Daniel T. (Box 75)
- Gibbons, John (Box 112)
  Biographical information. Alumnus (1954 Ph.D., Physics); Federal Office of Energy Conservation; White House Office of Science and Technology Policy
- Gibert, George G. (Box 20)
- Gibson, Jan (Box 20)
- Gibson, William Marion (Box 20)
- Giddings, Pauls (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Women's/African and African American Studies
- Gifford, James Fergus, Jr. (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: DUMC Archivist
- Gilbert, Allan (Box 20)
- Gilbert, Allan H. (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: English, died 4/26/1987
- Gilbert, Allan (Box 149)
- Gilbert, Katherine Everett (Box 20)
- Gilbert, Paula E. (Box 75)
- Gilboa, Eli (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: DUMC, 2001
- Gilgor, Robert E. (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Dermatology
- Gili, Mary Eidam (Mrs. Torrence A.) (Box 20)
- Gili, Mary Eidam (Mrs. Torrence A.) (Box 129)
- Gilkeson, Gary (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Arthritis Center
- Gillen, Paul N. (Box 20)
- Gillen, Paul N. (Box 129)
- Gillespie, Michael Allen (Box 75)
- Gillespie, Richard A. (Box 20)
- Gillham, Nicholas W. (Box 75)
- Gilliam, Bryan (Box 75)
- Gillin, David G. (Box 149)
- Gillin, Donald (Box 20)
- Gillin, Donald G. (Box 75)
- Gillin, John P. (Box 20)
- Gillin, John P. (Box 129)
- Gillis, Stephen Malcolm (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Public Policy; Vice Provost, Academic Affairs; Graduate School
- Gillmore, George W. (Box 20)
- Ginn, Fred L. (Box 20)
- Ginsberg, Brian (Box 75)
- Gionta, Ralph L. (Box 20)
- Gionta, Ralph Lawrence (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Planning Manager, Physical Plant, Retired 6/1987
- Giraldo, Zaida I. (Box 20)
- Giraldo, Zaida I. (Box 129)
- Gish, Annabeth (Box 112)
  Biographical information. Alumna; Actress (X-Files)
- Githens, Sherwood (Box 20)
- Githens, Sherwood (Box 149)
- Githens, Sherwood (Box 129)
- Gittler, Joseph B. (Box 75)
- Glander, Kenneth Earl (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biological Anthropology and Anatomy; Primate Center
- Glass, Peter (Box 75)
- Glasson, John (Box 20)
- Glasson, John (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Consulting Surgery
- Glasson, William Henry (Box 20)
- Gleckner, Robert F. (Box 75)
- Glenn, James F. (Box 20)
- Glenn, James Francis (Box 149)
- Glenn, James Francis (Box 75)
- Glenn, Thomas M. (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Health Affairs
- Glockler, George (Box 20)
- Glockler, George (Box 129)
- Glover-Wetherington, Miriam Anne (Box 75)
- Glower, Donald (Box 75)
- Gobbel, Ellen Huckabee (Box 20)
- Gobbel, Ellen Huckabee (Box 129)
- Godbey, Allen H. (Box 20)
- Godwin, David J. (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Transfusion Services Hemotherapy
- Godwin, Harold L. (Box 75)
- Goestenkors, Gail (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Women's Basketball Coach
- Goffen, Rona (Box 20)
- Goffen, Rona (Box 129)
- Gohdes, Clarence (Box 20)
- Gohdes, Clarence Louis Frank (Box 75)
- Gold, Deborah (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Research Psychology and Behavioral Science; Sociology
- Goldberg, Leon (Box 21)
- Goldberg, Mary Lucile "Marylu" (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychology, died 2001
- Goldberg, Ronald (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Neonatal-Perinatal Medicine, DUMC
- Goldin, Judah (Box 21)
- Golding, Martin P. (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Philosophy and Law; Philosophy Dept.
- Goldner, J. Leonard (Box 21)
- Goldner, J. Leonard (Box 75)
- Goldner, J. Leonard (Box 129)
- Goldner, Richard D. (Box 75)
- Goldschmidt, Pascal J. (Box 75)
- Goldsmith, Fred (Box 75)
- Goldsmith, Jewett (Box 21)
- Goldsmith, Jewett (Box 129)
- Goldsmith, Jewett (Box 149)
- Goldsmith, Lowell A. (Box 21)
- Goldstein, Larry (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Neurologist; Duke's Center for Cerebrovascular Disease
- Goldstone, Sanford (Box 21)
- Goldwater, Leonard J. (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Founder, Occupational Medicine, died 7/2/1992
- Golner, Geoffrey Robinson (Box 75)
- Goodall, McChesney, Jr. (Box 21)
- Goodall, McChesney, Jr. (Box 129)
- Goode, David (Box 112)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; Chairman, Norfolk Southern
- Goodling, Richard A. (Box 21)
- Goodling, Richard A. (Box 129)
- Goodman, Jim (Box 112)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; CEO, Capitol Broadcasting Co.
- Goodrich, Jack (Box 21)
- Goodrich, Jack (Box 129)
- Goodson, W. Kenneth (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Bishop, UMC; Trustee, Univ. and Endowment; Divinity Sch. Board of Visitors, died 9/17/1991
- Goodwin, Crauford David W. (Box 149)
- Goodwin, Crauford David W. (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Economics. Gradied Sch.; Vice Provost for Research
- Goodwyn, Lawrence Corbett (Box 75)
- Gopen, George D. (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: English; Writing Programs
- Gordon, Alexander (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Therapeutic Recreation Coordinator, Pediatric Units Support Service
- Gordon, Andrew (Box 75)
- Gordy, Walter, 2 folders (Box 21)
- Gordy, Walter (Box 149)
- Gordy, Walter (Box 129)
- Goree, John A. (Box 21)
- Goree, John A. (Box 129)
- Gosele, Ulrich M. (Box 75)
- Goshaw, Alfred T. (Box 75)
- Gotwals, Harry D. (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Vice President
- Grabowski, Henry George (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Economics; Economics ( 9/1989 - 8/1992)
- Grady, Tana (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychiatry and Behavioral Sciences; Medicine
- Graffagnino, Carmello (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Co-Neuro Critical Care Unit
- Graham, Daniel A. (Box 75)
- Graham, Doyle Gene (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pathology; Medical Education
- Graham, James Douglas (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Instructor, History
- Graham, John R. (Box 75)
- Graham, John W. (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Planning
- Graham, Lindsay Alexander (Box 21)
- Graham, Lindsay Alexander (Box 129)
- Graham, Tom (Box 21)
- Grandin, Greg (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: History, 2000
- Grandis, Arnold (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Perinatology
- Grane, George V. (Box 129)
- Granger, Christopher (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Cardiologist, Duke's Clinical Research Institute (DCRI)
- Grant, Augustus O. (Box 75)
- Grant, John P. (Box 75)
- Grant, Richard Babson (Box 21)
- Grant, Richard Babson (Box 149)
- Grant, Richard Babson (Box 75)
- Grant, Ruth (Box 75)
- Grant, Thomas M., Deceased 12-31-1952, Trustee (Box 116)
- Gratz, Pauline (Box 75)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Nursing, Retired 9/1/1985
- Graves, Robert Williams (Box 21)
- Gray, C. Jarrett, Jr. (Box 75)
- Gray, Edward Rutherford (Box 21)
- Gray, Irving E. (Box 129)
- Gray, Irving E. (Box 149)
- Gray, Irving E. (Box 75)
- Gray, Irving Emery (Box 21)
- Gray, Robert Earl (Box 21)
- Gray, Robert Earl (Box 129)
- Greeley, William J. (Box 76)
- Green, C. Sylvester (Box 21)
- Green, Capt. Richard F. (Box 76)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Commanding Officer, NROTC; Naval Science
- Green, Monica H. (Box 76)
- Green, Robert L. (Box 129)
- Green, Robert L., Jr. (Box 76)
- Green, Warner Craig (Box 76)
- Green, William L. (Box 21)
- Green, William L., Jr. (Box 129)
- Green, William L., Jr. (Box 76)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Public Relations, Retired 12/30/1986
- Greenberg, Charles S. (Box 76)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medicine; Pathology
- Greenberg, Michael L. (Box 76)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Res. General Surgery
- Greene, Ronald H. (Box 21)
- Greenfield, Joseph C., Jr. (Box 76)
- Greengrass, Roy A. (Box 76)
- Greenhill, Maurice H. (Box 21)
- Greenhill, Maurice H. (Box 76)
- Greenhill, Maurice H. (Box 129)
- Greenhill, Maurice H. (Box 150)
- Greenleaf, Arno L. (Box 76)
- Greenside, Henry (Box 76)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Computer Science; Physics
- Greenwood, Joseph A. (Box 130)
- Greenwood, Joseph A. (Box 76)
- Greenwood, Joseph A. (Box 150)
- Greer, Paul S. (Box 21)
- Greer, Paul S. (Box 130)
- Greer, Paul S. (Box 150)
- Gregg, John Richard (Box 76)
- Gregg, Robert A. (Box 21)
- Gregg, Robert A. (Box 150)
- Gregg, Robert Allen (Box 130)
- Gregg, Robert Allen (Box 76)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation
- Gregg, Robert C. (Box 21)
- Gregg, Robert C. (Box 76)
- Gregg, Robert C. (Box 130)
- Greggs, Gilbert A., Jr. (Box 76)
- Greuling, Eugene (Box 21)
- Greuling, Eugene (Box 130)
- Greuling, Eugene (Box 150)
- Grichnik, James M. (Box 76)
- Grichnik, Katherine (Box 76)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: DUMC, 2000
- Grieco, Joseph M. (Box 76)
- Griffin, Ernest Otto, Jr. (Box 21)
- Griffin, George (Box 76)
- Griffin, Gordon (Box 112)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; U.S. Ambassador to Canada
- Griffith, John (Box 21)
- Griffith, Kathleen, Trustee (Box 116)
- Griffith, William Jackson, III (Box 130)
- Griffith, William Jackson, III (Box 150)
- Griffith, William Jackson, III (Box 76)
- Griffiths, Phillip A. (Box 130)
- Griffiths, Phillip A. (Box 76)
- Griggs, Lillian Baker (Box 21)
- Griggs, Lillian Baker (Box 130)
- Griggs, Lillian Baker (Box 150)